

PROFILE

I was in the Navy for 6 years as a Reactor Operator, which required an eye for detail for safe reactor operations. While still in the Navy, I was also responsible for my ship's confidential computer system. Meaning I'm proficient in network and server administration in a Windows environment.

I also worked as a Customer Support Engineer which involved troubleshooting and repairing metrology tools in a clean-room environment.

All of those led me to have a solid grasp on the troubleshooting process, which makes me effective in detecting and fixing bugs.

I am going into web development due to a desire to expand into new skills that utilize my eye for detail, computer skills, and creativity.

CONTACT

PHONE: 843-323-5199

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kalyn-reid-a7a728163/

WEBSITE:

https://reidk361.github.io/Portfolio/

E-MAIL:

reidkalyn361@gmail.com

HOBBIES

- Digital Art
- Web Development

KALYN REID

ADMINISTRATIVE SUPPORT PERSONNEL

ASPIRING FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

Naval Nuclear Power Training Program, Nuclear Electronics Technician Jan 2015 – Dec 2016

University of Oregon Coding Bootcamp

Apr 2021 - Oct 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kroger – Administrative Support Personnel

Apr 2021 - Sep 2021

- Worked with Home Goods replenishment and School with tasks, such as creating sales, using IBM Personal Communications stocking software.
- Updated purchase trends for years' worth of data and vendor information by interfacing IBM Personal Communications and Microsoft Office Excel.

KLA-Tencor - Customer Support Engineer

Nov 2020 - Mar 2021

- Evaluated, analyzed, diagnosed and troubleshot technical equipment problems at the customer site.
- Repairs can involve board-level troubleshooting as well as system level problems which have multiple causes.
- Filed daily reports on status of tools and parts ordered at the end of each working day.

USS Nimitz - Propulsion Plant Local Area Network Administrator Mar 2019 – Nov 2020

- Became familiar and proficient at troubleshooting various issues with PPLAN and the software hosted on it.
- Became a Work Center Supervisor within a month of becoming part of the PPLAN work center.
 - Supervised, coordinated, and reviewed approx. 30 maintenance items a month.
 - o Maintained administrative readiness for ship and Reactor department audits.
 - Became Leading Petty Officer after 10 months of becoming Work Center Supervisor.

 o Led seven other sailors in the work center, five of which were higher ranking.
 - Taught and mentored several sailors in network and server administration.

USS Nimitz - Nuclear Electronics Technician

Feb 2017 - Nov 2020

- Performed regular preventative maintenance items on multiple Reactor Control and Protection systems to include alignments, alignment checks, and operational checks.
- Responsible for explaining equipment work and operations to multiple levels of authority.
- Composed and managed work documents and records for maintenance, troubleshooting and repair of Reactor Plant electronic equipment.
- Trained peers and subordinates on equipment knowledge and operations to support Navy Nuclear qualifications and continuous training.
- Additional qualifications: Craftsman, 3M, and COMSEC

SKILLS

- Maintenance Planning and Streamlinina
- Reliable in Reactor Plant Operations
- Virtual Machine and Server Cluster Administration
- Accurate Data Entry

- Trend Analysis
- Troubleshooting
- Team Leadership
- Microsoft Office Suite Literacy
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript